<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Go Journey on Lyon&#39;s Field Notes</title>
    <link>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Go Journey on Lyon&#39;s Field Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The sexism of &#39;sexism&#39;</title>
      <link>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/171019-sexism-is-discrimination-against-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/171019-sexism-is-discrimination-against-men/</guid>
      <description>To connoisseurs of feminist absurdity, the Oxford Dictionary&amp;rsquo;s definition of sexism is a gem. Any oversimplified claim that something is &amp;ldquo;typical&amp;rdquo; is a stereotype. So if sexism is stereotyping men and women, then claiming that sexism is &amp;ldquo;typically against women&amp;rdquo; is sexist.
The Oxford Dictionary&amp;rsquo;s definition of sexism is&amp;mdash;by its own definition&amp;mdash;sexist.
It&amp;rsquo;s not alone. Look at how three major dictionaries define and illustrate sexism:
Cambridge Dictionary:
 sexism (noun) (actions based on) the belief that the members of one sex are less intelligent, able, skilful, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feminism and false rape allegations</title>
      <link>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/170905-feminist-and-false-rape-allegations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 22:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/170905-feminist-and-false-rape-allegations/</guid>
      <description>Jemma Beale (25) was found guilty in July in Southwark Crown Court of making a series of false allegations of serious sexual assault and rape against fifteen men over a four year period. One falsely convicted man served two years of a seven year prison sentence in 2011 after the Crown Prosecution Service’s second attempt to secure his conviction on her behalf. Another was falsely arrested after being forced to flee the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the hammer, everything is a nail</title>
      <link>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/170812-to-the-hammer-everything-is-a-nail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/170812-to-the-hammer-everything-is-a-nail/</guid>
      <description>Korean car manufacturer Hyundai Motor UK recently conducted a study of 1,000 UK drivers “to better understand what impacts people’s behaviour when they are driving”. It found that women are on average 12 per cent angrier than men while behind the wheel of a car1.
That anger can manifest itself in road rage, and female perpetrators of road rage can be murderous. For example, a Manchester mother of two struck another vehicle with a golf club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lies, Damn Lies, and Renewable Energy statistics</title>
      <link>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/160712-lies-damn-lies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 07:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/160712-lies-damn-lies/</guid>
      <description>Proponents of sustainable energy arrangements (of which I am one) face a difficult challenge&amp;mdash;reconciling the the fundamental incompatibility between the low grade1, intermittency, and high cost of current renewable energy technologies with the requirement of industrial economies for energy sources which are high grade, continuously available, and inexpensive.
In our efforts to build confidence, mobilise support, and accelerate transition, we are inclined to refract the statistics of renewable technologies through glasses of the rosiest hue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love my female privilege...</title>
      <link>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/160516-i-love-my-female-privilege/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/160516-i-love-my-female-privilege/</guid>
      <description>There is no shortage of material ridiculing feminism. This is a classic.
   I love my female privilege, that I can go to college campuses where I’m the majority, provided I take retarded subjects like film theory, women’s studies, dance therapy, or pottery. If I go into Science, Technology, Engineering, or Maths, well, then I’m a minority and I&amp;rsquo;m oppressed, and you’re the oppressor, and we have to fix it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A load of balls</title>
      <link>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/151203-drawing-spheres/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/151203-drawing-spheres/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d like to learn to draw. So I&amp;rsquo;ve bought Kister&amp;rsquo;s You Can Draw in 30 Days: The Fun, Easy Way to Learn to Draw in One Month or Less. In it, he asks you to draw a plane, a house, and a bagel before you start the course. Here they are. These are all drawn on an iPad Pro, using an Apple Pencil and Procreate. They are rubbish.
 Initial Test</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminalising anti-feminism</title>
      <link>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/2015-02-14-criminalising-antifeminism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2015 07:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/2015-02-14-criminalising-antifeminism/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m an egalitarian&amp;mdash;I believe that men and women are equal and deserve equal rights and opportunities.
So I can&amp;rsquo;t agree with feminism&amp;mdash;the belief that women are entitled to preferential treatment today to compensate for the wrongs of yesterday1.
Now, I don&amp;rsquo;t know if you agree with my view. But I hold it in good faith, with as much concern for issues that affect women as I have for the issues that affect men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monument Valley, AZ</title>
      <link>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/100913-monument-valley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/posts/100913-monument-valley/</guid>
      <description>I arrived late in the evening at Monument Valley, tired from the long drive from Bryce Canyon. I pitched my tent on a narrow strip of sand next to the Navajo visitor centre car park, and fell asleep.
I woke at dawn to this view&amp;mdash;the iconic backdrop of the cowboy movies of my childhood. I felt the usual prickle of not-quite-recognition that attended much of my drive round the US that year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lyonsfieldnotes.org/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>